The kind of funny thing about Python, in languages like Java, you're required to make
getters and setters to modify stuff within your class, but Python is a little bit more
willy-nilly. So, I can just go and change the value of dot runs for my Subaru, for my instance.
I don't necessarily need to use a getter or setter. Using them is, you know, a best practice
in software projects to take out some of the mystery, but you're not going to get a syntaxer,
or Python is not going to stop you from doing this type of modification. So, now, if I call
my Subaru dot start, and it takes a name, so I'm going to have to pass one in again.
What will I see printed out?
All is broken. Time to do more front-end master's classes to pay for the repair.
Okay, so self- that's self-variable, it refers to an instance.
And if I make a new car, let's call it a Mustang car.
If I check runs on Mustang car, what will I get? It's true, right?
So, the changes that I made to my Subaru only applied to the my Subaru instance.